<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Becca Lynch</title><link>https://beccalynch.com/</link><description>Recent content in About on Becca Lynch</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://beccalynch.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://beccalynch.com/blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://beccalynch.com/blog/</guid><description>Blog 1.27.2022 - The Pleasure of Pointless Walks In the middle of our company’s holiday shutdown, I found myself going for a walk like I do most days. In an attempt to maximize my time, I was listening to an audiobook that promised to have the secrets to unlocking burnout and stress. In truth, so far, the book had done very little, other than detailing all the ways that stress is caused by the patriarchy (I’m sure it is) while ironically framing women’s stress almost entirely in the context of marriage and motherhood.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://beccalynch.com/blog_posts/pyodide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://beccalynch.com/blog_posts/pyodide/</guid><description>Interactive Online Plotting with Pyodide &amp;amp; Plotly</description></item><item><title/><link>https://beccalynch.com/books/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://beccalynch.com/books/</guid><description>Currently Reading The Maidens Michaelides, Alex The Diet Myth: The Real Science Behind What We Eat Spector, Tim Solutions and Other Problems Brosh, Allie Previously Read Anxious People Backman, Fredrik
5 / 5 Read the review The Art of Rest: How to Find Respite in the Modern Age Hammond, Claudia</description></item><item><title/><link>https://beccalynch.com/resume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://beccalynch.com/resume/</guid><description>Work Duo Security Senior Data Scientist Senior researcher on Duo&amp;rsquo;s Algorithms Research team, leading research initiatives for model improvement. Leading geospatial anomaly detection research, from initial literature review through current deployment and development. Coordinating and collaborating with product and leadership on customer discussions to guide future product directions. Data Scientist (2019-2021) Researcher and developer on Duo Trust Monitor, an anomaly detection platform. Continuously iterated on threat detection models to improve detection precision, including geospatial modeling research and automated model drift detection.</description></item></channel></rss>